<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Literally Just Recipes</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Literally Just Recipes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:53:49 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Peanut Butter Walnut Oatmeal Cookies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/peanut-butter-walnut-oatmeal-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 19:53:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/peanut-butter-walnut-oatmeal-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Rich and nutty.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup shelled walnuts (halves or pieces)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 1/2 cups spelt or whole wheat flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons baking soda&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 teaspoon kosher salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup (packed) dark brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, at room temperature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup chunky peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups rolled oats (ideally, extra thiccc)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;kosher or flaky sea salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add walnuts to food processor and processor until very fine - almost buttery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add butter and both sugars to the bowl of a stand mixer with flat or paddle beater. Beat at low speed until combined, then increase speed and beat until fluffy (2-3 minutes).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add walnuts, peanut butter, eggs, and vanilla, mix until combined.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower the speed so the flour doesn&amp;rsquo;t fly out and blend in flour, baking soda, and salt until combined. Mix at high speed for about another minute.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add oats, mix until combined.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Line a large, flat pan with parchment paper (for chilling, not for baking). Scoop the dough into ~2 tbsp balls and lay them out on the pan; they can be almost touching. Lightly dust with large-grain salt. Cover with plastic wrap. Chill in fridge for at least 3 hours, up to overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When ready to bake, preheat oven to 375F.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Line a cookie sheet with parchment paper. Arrange the cookies on the sheet, leaving about an inch of space between them. Bake until lightly golden and still soft; ~10 minutes. Remove immediately and transfer to cooling racks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pumpkin Rugelach</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/pumpkin-rugelach/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 11:04:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/pumpkin-rugelach/</guid>
      <description>Sage and walnuts pair with pumpkin for a savory appetizer.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 oz cream cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon kosher salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp extra virgin olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 cup finely chopped fresh sage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp chopped savory, fresh or dried&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 large shallots, finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 tsp aleppo or chili flakes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup pure pumpkin puree&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 pinches kosher salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pinch black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup walnuts finely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flakey salt and/or finely shredded parmesan cheese for sprinkling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the dough: Cut the butter and cream cheese into ~tbsp sized pats and let soften for ~15m. Pulse flour and salt in food processer, then add butter and cream cheese and pulse several times, until the mixture has formed large crumbly chunks. Gather the dough into 2 large balls, flatten into disks and wrap in plastic wrap. Refrigerate for at least 2 hours, up to overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the filling: Head 3tbsp EVOO in large skillet until shimmering. Add shallots, sage, savory, and pepper flakes and cook until fragrant (~2min). Stir in the pumpkin puree and cook ~5m more to reduce water. Season with kosher salt and black pepper. Remove from heat and cool to room temperature.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven to 350. Roll each dough disk into a 12&amp;quot; circle on floured surface. Use lots of flour under it to avoid sticking. Mix the chopped walnuts into the filling, then spread half of the filling onto each disk. Cut each disk into 16 triangles. Roll each one starting from the wide end to form a crescent. Place on cookie sheet lined with parchment paper.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beat the egg with 1 tsp water and brush lightly on each rugelach. Top each with flaky sea salt and/or grated parmesan. Bake for ~27m until golden brown. Serve warm if possible. Makes 32 small rugelach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chocolate Chip Walnut Cookies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chocolate-chip-walnut-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 16:54:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/chocolate-chip-walnut-cookies/</guid>
      <description>This is the best chocolate chip cookie recipe in the universe, as far as I am aware.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup (2 sticks) unsalted butter, softened&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/4 cup + 1 tbsp granulated sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/4 cup light brown sugar (packed)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 large eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 1/4 tsp vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 tsp lemon juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 1/4 cups all purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup rolled oats or instant oatmeal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp baking soda&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pinch cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 2/3 cups semi sweet chocolate chips&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 3/4 cups chopped walnuts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Line 2 large baking sheets with parchment paper (if you do not have 2 large baking sheets, you&amp;rsquo;ll have to bake in batches).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cream butter and sugars together in a stand mixer until light and fluffy, scraping sides as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beat in the eggs, vanilla, and lemon juice until fully incorporated, scraping sides as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lower the speed so the flour doesn&amp;rsquo;t fly out and blend in flour, oats, baking soda, cinammon, and salt until evenly mixed into a thick, sticky batter.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a soft spatula, fold in chocolate chips and walnuts until evently distributed in the dough.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a large ice cream scoop or cookie scoop, scoop out a rough (3-ish tbsp) hemisphere of dough at a time and place on parchment-paper-lined baking sheets, leaving about 3 inches between neighbors. Do not flatten or shape cookies; they will flatten out as they bake.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover the prepared cookie sheets with plastic wrap so the dough doesn&amp;rsquo;t dry out, and chill in the fridge for at least an hour or up to overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When ready to start baking, preheat oven to 300F.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bake the cookie sheet(s) in oven until the cookies look just dry on top; they should still appear soft and underbaked. The bake will probably take 15-20 minutes but you want to start checking the cookie tops by 15 minutes at the latest. Remove immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow to cool and set for at least 10 minutes on the hot, parchment-paper-covered cookie sheet after removing from oven.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When set, remove to a board or tray or other flat surface (not a rack). You can serve them immediately while still warm, or transfer to an airtight container to store. They will be delicious at any temperature, but to re-warm, you can microwave your cookie(s) for roughly 8 seconds.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peanut Butter Miso Cookies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/peanut-butter-miso-cookies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:17:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/peanut-butter-miso-cookies/</guid>
      <description>Miso adds a savory richness to soft peanut butter cookies.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;dough&#34;&gt;Dough&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 1/2 cups all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp baking powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp baking soda&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup unsalted butter, softened&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/4 cup creamy peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp white miso&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 cup white granulated sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;for-coating&#34;&gt;For Coating&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 cup granulated sugar or large-grain sugar (such as demarara)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp sesame seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven to 350. Line 2 baking sheets with parchment paper and set aside. Mix together the sugar and sesame seeds for coating in a plate or shallow bowl, set aside.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a medium bowl, whisk together flour, baking powder, and baking soda.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add the softened butter, peanut butter, and miso to a mixer bowl. With the paddle attachment, mix together until smooth.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Add brown sugar, white sugar, and vanilla to the mixer. Mix until smooth and creamy. Add in the egg and mix again until evenly incorporated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set the mixer to low and slowly pour in the flour mixture (so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fly out). Mix until evenly incorporated.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remove the dough from the mixture and scoop and roll it into roughly 1-inch balls. Roll each ball in the sugar/sesame mix until roughly coated; place them on your parchment-paper covered baking sheets about 4 inches apart.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;With a fork, flatten each ball in a criss-cross pattern until it forms a cookie shape on the baking sheet, about half an inch thick.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bake one sheet at a time. For each sheet, bake for 9-11 minutes, until edges are just slightly golden brown (the cookies will still be very soft). Remove from oven and allow to cool on the baking sheet for 5 minutes, then transfer to a wire rack. Serve as soon as they are cool enough to eat, or store in an airtight container.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Savory French Toast Skillet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/savory-french-toast-skillet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 17:46:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/savory-french-toast-skillet/</guid>
      <description>A flavorful, hearty breakfast main to feed a crowd with.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 loaf herbal focaccia&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup chopped spinach (fresh or frozen)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup basil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 cloves garlic, minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp red pepper flakes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp thyme&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp oregano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ground black pepper,  to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 oz grated Romano cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 oz grated Parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flaky sea salt, to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Chopped parsley for garnish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cube the focaccia and allow the cubes to dry out, overnight or over up to several days.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In a large bowl, beat together the eggs, spinach, basil, garlic, herbs, red pepper, black pepper, and Romano cheese. Pour over the dried focaccia cubes and allow to soak for at least 30 minutes or up to overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven to 350F.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat an oven-safe cast iron skillet on the stove over medium heat. Add the butter to the skillet and allow to melt and coat the bottom of the skillet.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pour the egg and bread mixture into the heated, greased skillet. Top with the Parmesan and flaky salt to taste.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Place the skillet in the oven and bake for 30-40 minutes until the top is golden brown and a fork inserted in the middle comes out clean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Garnish with parsley and serve hot with any sweet and savory sauces.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;* Adjustments: chopped, precooked bacon or breakfast sausage, roasted veggies like tomatoes, onion, mushrooms,  or peppers, or any other fresh herbs or cheeses you have available would all be great additions. I normally throw in a few dashes of a nice hot sauce as well&amp;ndash;not enough to overpower the flavors but enough to add some zip.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pecan Pie Bars</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/pecan-pie-bars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 11:52:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/pecan-pie-bars/</guid>
      <description>Pecan pie, but in bite-sized bar form.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;crust&#34;&gt;Crust&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7/8 cups all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/8 cup butter, softened&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp pecans, coarsely chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;filling&#34;&gt;Filling&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/3 cup firmly packed brown sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp all-purpose flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/4 cup dark corn syrup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 large eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp vanilla extract&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3/4 cup coarsely chopped pecans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 tsp instant espresso or instant coffee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven to 350.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the crust. Combine flour, butter and sugar for crust in bowl. Beat at medium speed, scraping often, until mixture resembles coarse crumbs. Stir in pecans for crust.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Press crust mixture evenly into bottom of ungreased 7x11 baking pan. Bake 18-22 minutes or until edges are very light golden brown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;While crust bakes, make the filling. Combine brown sugar, flour, instant espresso/coffee, and salt in large bowl; whisk until mixed. Add corn syrup, eggs, and vanilla; mix well. Stir in pecans. Spread evenly over hot, partially baked crust. Return to the oven; bake another 30-35 minutes until filling is set and a knife inserted in the bars comes out clean.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow to cool; refrigerate at least 30 minutes. Optionally, sprinkle with powdered sugar. Cut into bars and serve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 11:30:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of things on this website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of things that are not on this website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long rambling stories about how the recipe came from somebody&amp;rsquo;s uncle&amp;rsquo;s ex&amp;rsquo;s dog&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser&amp;rsquo;s great-great-grandmother&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long rambling introductory sections about the proper technique with which to boil water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;popups of any sort&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;j*v*scr*pt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like it, bookmark or make some of the recipes, or share them with your friends and relations. If you really like, feel free to email me recipe submissions at tomwarner13 at gmail dot com. If this really takes off I&amp;rsquo;ll develop a more scalable submission method.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of things on this website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;recipes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here is a list of things that are not on this website:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ads&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;videos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long rambling stories about how the recipe came from somebody&amp;rsquo;s uncle&amp;rsquo;s ex&amp;rsquo;s dog&amp;rsquo;s hairdresser&amp;rsquo;s great-great-grandmother&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;long rambling introductory sections about the proper technique with which to boil water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;popups of any sort&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;j*v*scr*pt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you like it, bookmark or make some of the recipes, or share them with your friends and relations. If you really like, feel free to email me recipe submissions at tomwarner13 at gmail dot com. If this really takes off I&amp;rsquo;ll develop a more scalable submission method.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you don&amp;rsquo;t like it, that&amp;rsquo;s perfectly fine. There are lots of recipe sites on the rest of the internet filled with non-recipe content.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The source code lives &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/tomwarner13/literallyjustrecipes&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; if you&amp;rsquo;re a nerd. If you&amp;rsquo;re a mega-nerd, you can even open a PR for me and I&amp;rsquo;ll probably merge it.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harissa Glazed Carrots</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/recipes/harissa-glazed-carrots/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 10:33:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/recipes/harissa-glazed-carrots/</guid>
      <description>Roasted carrots with a spicy-sweet glaze served over creamy labneh.</description>
      <content>&lt;h2 id=&#34;ingredients&#34;&gt;Ingredients&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 lbs whole carrots, washed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup harissa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/4 cup honey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp coriander&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp cumin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp smoked paprika&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp dried aleppo pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup full-fat yogurt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp table salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chopped parsley leaves, for garnish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;instructions&#34;&gt;Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the labneh: line a colander with cheesecloth or several layers of paper towels, and set it over a bowl to drain. Mix the salt into the yogurt and add the yogurt to the colander. Allow to drain on counter or in refrigerator for at least 3 hours or up to overnight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make the glaze: mix the harissa, olive oil, honey, coriander, cumin, aleppo, and smoked paprika in a bowl.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preheat oven to 375. Roughly chop the carrots into 3-ish inch pieces; halve or quarter any thick sections so that all the pieces are a similar width.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set a large pot of heavily salted water to boil. When the water boils, add the carrots and parboil for 5 minutes. Remove carrots from water immediately.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Divide the glaze in half. When the carrots are cool enough to handle, toss them in half the glaze, coating evenly. Spread the carrots out on a baking pan lined with parchment paper and roast for about 40 minutes, turning once, until carrots are soft and outsides have begun to brown.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shmear the labneh roughly across a large serving tray. Spread the finished carrots on the labneh, and drizzle them with the remaining glaze. Garnish with parsley leaves and serve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
